

Pejman Kiamehr

Junior Front-End Developer with React

Summary

Experienced React Developer with over 1 year of experience in designing and building organizational panels as well as developing websites, primarily focusing on front-end development. Currently seeking an opportunity with an active and dynamic company to contribute to project development and further enhance personal skills. Strong preference for being part of a team with multiple front-end developers.

Contact Information

Phone 0915 550 3369

Email pejman.kiamehr@gmail.com

Work samples

MyWebsite www.pejmankiamehr.ir

Github https://github.com/pejmankiamehr

Technical Skills

 $fundamentals \quad HTML, CSS, JavaScript, E6, Responsive \ Design$

ReactJs ContextAPI,React-Router,Styled-Component,MaterialUI,AntDesing,TailwindCSS,hooks,axios

VC Git, Github, Gitlab

Others Scrum, postman, api, Webpack, Media-Query, Bootstrap, JQuery, JQuery-UI, Less, trello, Latex

Professional Experiences

2021–2022 Front end developer, Mashhad.

• Eight Team

2018–2020 **Customer affairs expert**, *Tehran*.

Romak Holding (Snapp Team)

2016–2017 Website admin, Mashhad.

Yekta Mana Company

2015–2016 Content production specialist, Mashhad.

Yekta Mana Company

Education

2019–2020 **Tehran Institute of Technology**, *Tehran*.

Web Package Design 1,2,3

2009-2013 Islamic Azad University, Mashhad.

BSc. of Mechanical Engineering

Soft skills

- 1. Embraces teamwork
- 2. Excellent written and verbal communication skills
- 3. Excellent presentation and negotiation skills
- 4. Team-oriented personality